tell.com 2010-12-31

# TELL | Privacy Policy

TELL.com has created this Privacy Statement (Policy) in order to demonstrate TELL.com's commitment to help our users better understand what information TELL.com collects about them and what may happen to that information. 

The following discloses TELL.com's information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites listed below. 

## Overview

As part of the normal operation of TELL.com's services we collects and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information TELL.com collects about you and what may happen to that information. By accepting this Privacy Policy and TELL.com's Terms of Use, you expressly consent to TELL.com's use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms of Use.   
This Privacy Statement applies to all related sites. All other worldwide sites operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy, and subject to the requirements of applicable local law, TELL.com strives to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the sites. 

## 1.A Special Note About Children

  * TELL.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, you must have your parent or guardian's permission before you use our sites.

## 2.Information TELL.com Collect

  * Registration - Required Information:   
When you register for a TELL.com account, TELL.com requires you to provide the following: 
  
(a)Display Name:   
a name that is always publicly displayed. You can change your display name whenever you want in your account setting page. 

(b)Password:   
is required for signing into your TELL.com account. Your password provides access to all of the information in your account, so never share your password with anyone except a parent or guardian. 

(c)E-mail:   
an email address is required so that TELL.com can contact you about your account. Confirmation will be sent to the email to confirm the account. You can change the email in your account setting page. Your email address is never publicly displayed on TELL.com. 

  * Account Setting / Profile Information:
After you have registered for a TELL.com account, you are given the opportunity to fill out information on our account setting page. Filling out the setting page is optional - you are not required to fill out any of the profile information. If you choose to fill out the profile information, please note that this information will be posted and will potentially be accessible to the entire world. 
  * Service Usage:
Information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads. Information about the submitted stories / posts or reply. 
  * Cookies:
we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to TELL.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 
  * Log information:
Information such as your? web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request. 
  * Correspondence Information:
TELL.com allows users to interact by replying on stories / posts. Content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services. 

## 3.TELL.com's Use of your information

  * All materials (without limitation) include text and image regardless of whether the content is included in post, profile, comments, or any other portion or feature of TELL.com, may be used throughout the site. 
  * Due to the public nature of TELL.com, we highly recommended our users select the information they will disclose carefully.
  * Non-personally identifiable information such as IP-based location or browser type may be used in our statistical analysis of how our site is used.
  * We may share your non-personally identifiable information with third-party service providers, including advertisers, in order to improve the products and services provided on TELL.com.

## 4.Disclosure or your information

  * Due to the existing regulatory environment, TELL.com cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), TELL.com may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from TELL.com. Therefore, although TELL.com uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, TELL.com does not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.
  * As a matter of policy, TELL.com does not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.
  
(a)Advertisers:   
TELL.com aggregates (gather up data across all TELL.com's users' accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, TELL.com does not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. TELL.com may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on TELL.com's behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

(b)Other Corporate Entities:   
TELL.com share much of TELL.com's data, including personally identifiable information about you, with TELL.com's parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other members. TELL.com's parent and/or subsidiaries will follow privacy practices no less protective of all members than TELL.com's practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that TELL.com and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that TELL.com would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) and TELL.com will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

(c)Legal Requests:   
TELL.com cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. TELL.com can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as TELL.com, in TELL.com's sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability. 

## 5.Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Profile

  * Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration through the Account Setting Page including: your password and e-mail address. You can also change your information such as: display name, profile image,user url (allow to set once), location, industry, role, gender, birthday.
  * TELL.com will retain in TELL.com's files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce TELL.com's terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from TELL.com's databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from TELL.com's databases in response to your requests.

## 6.Control of your Password

  * You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. Therefore TELL.com do not recommend that you disclose your your password or login information to any third parties. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

## 7.Other Information Collectors

  * Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information TELL.com collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on TELL.com or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that TELL.com use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies.

## 8.Security

  * Your personally identifiable information security is largely dependent on your protection of your account password. You should never share your account password to unauthorized people.

## 9.Notice

  * TELL.com may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and TELL.com's need to accurately reflect TELL.com's data collection and disclosure practices. All changes to this policy are effective without notice to you.

## 10.Contact Us

  * If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact [info@tell.com](mailto:info@tell.com).
